Guide to the Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel Collection, 1876-2020 and undated, bulk 1950-2020 RL.10006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal, 1923-2019; undated
  - Personal Aesthetics, 1960-2019; undated; 5
    Subseries contains correspondence, notes, clippings, printed materials, photographs, fabric samples, and many folders of appraisals for art, furnishings, and cultural artifacts, all related to Diamonstein-Spielvogel's properties, interior furnishings and decor, and collections. Arranged alphabetically by folder title. For the most part, original folder titles have been retained.
    - Antique furniture, 1983-1988; undated (Box 100)
    - Apartment furnishings, 1981-1988; 2 folders (Box 100)
    - Attire, 1983-2003 (Box 100)
    - Chihuly studio, 2002 (Box 100)
    - Christie's correspondence, 1981; 2006 (Box 100)
    - Consignments, 1994 (Box 100)
    - Consignment, home furnishing, tailoring (Box 72)
    - Facsimiles, Ltd. catalog, 1988 (Box 100)
    - Furniture-720 Park Avenue, 1983-1984 (Box 100)
    - Furniture-720 Park Avenue, 1999-2000 (Box 100)
    - Home and auction, 1997-1998 (Box 101)
    - Home and auction, 1999-2006 (Box 101)
    - Home decor, 1963-1999; 5 folders (Box 101)
    - Home design, 1986-2003; undated; 3 folders (Box 102)
    - Home furnishings, 1960s; 3 folders (Box 102)
    - Home furnishings, 1973; 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Home furnishings, 1973-1974 (Box 102)
    - Home furnishings, 1984-1985; 3 folders (Box 102)
    - Home furnishings: purchases, 1986-1987 (Box 103)
    - Home furnishings: appraisal, 1987; 4 folders (Box 103)
    - Home furnishings: samples, 1988-1994 (Box 103)
    - Home furnishings, 1988-1994; folder 1 of 3 (Box 103)
    - Home furnishings, 1988-1994; folders 2-3 of 3 (Box 104)
    - Home furnishings, circa 1991-2005 (Box 104)
    - Home furnishings, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 104)
    - Home furnishings, 1998-2006; undated; 6 folders (Box 105)
    - Home furnishings by room: 1st floor, undated (Box 105)
    - Home furnishings by room: 2nd floor, undated (Box 105)
    - Home furnishings by room: 3rd floor, undated (Box 106)
    - Home furnishings by room: 4th floor, undated (Box 106)
    - Home furnishings by room: Majolica and Chihuly, undated (Box 106)
    - Home furnishings by room: miscellaneous, undated (Box 106)
    - Home furnishings by room: negatives, undated (Box 106)
    - Home furnishings by room: outside, undated (Box 106)
    - House and garden dishes, undated (Box 106)
    - House sketch, undated (Box 106)
    - House materials, Gin Lane, 1998-1999 (Box 106)
    - Household, 1983 (Box 107)
    - Landscaping and decor invoices, 1986 (Box 107)
    - Marders Nursery, 1994 (Box 107)
    - Matouk and Company, 1994 (Box 107)
    - Personal price lists, 2003 (Box 107)
    - Pound Ridge home, 1985-1987; 3 folders (Box 107)
    - Pound Ridge home, blueprints, 1986; 1 folders (Box 617)
    - Pound Ridge, New York, 1987 (Box 107)
    - Pound Ridge, New York, scrapbook of construction photographs, 1960s-1980s (Box 617)
    - Residence, New York, 2001-2003 (Box 108)
    - Southampton, New York survey, 1992 (Box 108)
    - Southampton, New York residence, 1993 (Box 108)
    - Southampton, New York residence, blueprints, 1998 (Box 108)
    - Southampton, New York, 2001 (Box 108)
    - Southampton, New York photographs, printed material, 2008 (Box 108)
    - 5th Avenue apartment layout, undated (Box 71)
    - 71 Main Street, Southampton, NY, house hunt/purchase 2015 (Box 617)
    - 72nd St. Apt. general, 2005-2007 (Box 108)
    - 72nd St. Apt. by room, 2005-2007 (Box 108)
    - 720 Park Avenue, Silver Rail Construction, 2006 (Box 108)
    - 720 Park Avenue listing/floorplan, 2019 (Box 653)
    - Southampton photo album, undated (Box 617)
  - Photographs, 1923-2013; undated; 6
    Files in the subseries house many black-and-white and color photographs and slides. Subjects include family members, friends, and artwork, as well as personal events and vacations covering a period of time from before Diamonstein-Spielvogel's birth to 2008. Highlights include early black-and-white portraits of Diamonstein-Spielvogel's family, the Dworkins. Other photographs are located throughout the collection.
    The subseries is arranged in two folder groups: the first arranged alphabetically by folder title; the other chronologically by year, with undated materials at the end. Most titles have been supplied by the project archivist.
    - Abroad, 1989; undated; 2 folders (Box 109)
    - Abroad, undated; 2 folders (Box 109)
    - Barbaralee Dworkin Diamonstein art, 1983 (Box 109)
    - Calgary Olympics, album from Frank Bennack, Jr., 1988 (Box 617)
    - Dance, undated (Box 109)
    - Family/friends, 1928; 1979; undated (Box 109)
    - Family/friends, 1983; 2000 (Box 110)
    - Family/personal events, 1989; undated (Box 110)
    - Family, New York City, undated (Box 110)
    - Family, 1923-1959; undated (Box 110)
    - Family, circa 1932, 1935; undated (Box 110)
    - Family, Sally née Alexansky and Rubin Dworkin, undated; 3 folders (Box 110)
    - Family and friends, undated (Box 617)
    - Gladys Cole family, undated (Box 110)
    - Head shots, family photos, notable figures, circa 1950-1972 (Box 110)
    - Insurance, 2002; folders 1-4 of 5 (Box 111)
    - Insurance, 2002; folder 5 of 5 (Box 112)
    - Insurance, 2008; 2 folders (Box 112)
    - Mixed artwork, slides, undated (Box 112)
    - New Year's Eve clipping, 1975; undated (Box 112)
    - Panama trip, 2012 (Box 68)
    - Personal gatherings, undated (Box 112)
    - Pi Alpha Tau, 1950 (Box 112)
    - Prince Charles and Princess Diana, undated (Box 112)
    - Slides, several events, undated (Box 112)
    - Slides, Rory McCarthy, 1983-1984 (Box 113)
    - Spielvogel home in Architectural Digest, 1995 (Box 113)
    - Travel/children, undated (Box 113)
    - Travel/friends, approximately 2008-2012 (Box 68)
    - Vacation slides, 1969 (Box 113)
    - Wedding, 1981; 2 folders (Box 113)
    - 1936-1967 and undated (Box 113)
    - Circa 1961-1981 (Box 113)
    - 1963 and undated (Box 113)
    - 1965-1973 (Box 113)
    - 1967-2009 and undated (Box 113)
    - 1978-1984 and undated (Box 113)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 113)
    - 1981-2008 and undated (Box 113)
    - 1989-1992, 2 folders (Box 114)
    - 1993 and undated (Box 114)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 114)
    - 1999, 2001; undated (Box 114)
    - 2004 and undated (Box 114)
    - 2015 and undated (Box 77)
    - 2016 and undated, 2 folders (Box 71)
    - Undated, folder 1 of 7 (Box 114)
    - Undated, folders 2-7 of 7 (Box 115)
    - Undated (Box 72)
    - Photographs/slides, undated (Box 115)
    - Photograph albums, 1980s-1990s (Box 609)
      Albums include snapshots from travels to China (1984), Peru, and Java (1997) as well as Southampton construction (1994), Pound Ridge house (1987), and undated photos from trips to Java (1997), Thailand, Cambodia (1995), Jordan, Wyoming, India (1996), and Haiti (1997). Also includes photographs of Cuomo, DNC, White House/Clinton inauguration, and photographs of the Southampton property.
    - Photograph albums, 1980s-1990s (Box 615)
    - Photograph albums, 1980s-1990s (Box 610)
    - Slovakia, other unidentified places, 2001 (Box 617)
    - Diamonstein-Spielvogel and VIPs, 1990s-2000s (Box 617)
    - Vacations, personal photographs, historical family photographs, 7 folders (Box 617)
    - Home art, decor, other objects, 1993; undated (Box 617)
  - Carl Spielvogel, 1953-2010; undated; 7
    Subseries consists of folders assembled and maintained by Diamonstein-Spielvogel that document the life and work of her husband Carl Spielvogel. Materials include correspondence, notes, printed matter, photographs, clippings, and awards and certificates, as well as a small amount of personal correspondence and other manuscript materials. The earliest materials predate their acquaintance; the couple married in 1981.
    Spielvogel is an international business executive who began working as a journalist for The New York Times and later became a leader in the advertising business working with Backer Spielvogel and Bates, Incorporated. He served as the U.S. Ambassador to the Slovak Republic from 2000-2001.
    Other materials pertaining to Spielvogel's appointment as Ambassador are located in the Ambassador Subseries of the Professional Series. Some materials related to Carl Spielvogel are also located in the General Working Files Subseries of the Personal Series and are scattered throughout the collection.
    Carl Spielvogel's professional papers documenting his advertising and political career are housed at the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising and Marketing History at Duke University.
    Arranged alphabetically by folder title. Original folder titles are retained.
    - A Small Agency That's No Small Beer (news article), 1981 (Box 115)
    - Advertising Women of the Year Award presented to Carl Spielvogel, 1977 (Box 115)
    - Ambassadorial publicity photographs and other images of Carl Spielvogel, circa 2001 and undated (Box 115)
    - Backer Spielvogel Bates, 1989-1991 (Box 115)
    - Backer Spielvogel Bates, Worldwide promotional materials, undated (Box 116)
    - Backer Spielvogel Bates Worldwide reception, 1993 (Box 116)
    - Baruch College Degree of Laws, 1984 (Box 116)
    - Baruch College Doctor of Laws, honorary degree, Carl Spielvogel, 1984 (Box 124)
    - Bratislava photographs, 2001 (Box 116)
    - Byelorussia pamphlet, circa 1975 (Box 116)
    - Citizen's Union distinguished service award, 1980 (Box 116)
    - Clippings, correspondence, awards, print materials, speeches 1974-1993, 2 folders (Box 116)
    - Control, 1993 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence, 1977; 1981-1995; 2002-2010; 3 folders (Box 116)
    - Golden Medal of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Slovak Republic, 2001 (Box 116)
      Folder contains certificate and programs; not the medal itself
    - Guest book, The Slovak Republic, 2000 (Box 117)
    - Publicity head shots, undated (Box 117)
    - International Herald Tribune, undated (Box 117)
    - Man of the Year Award, 1993 (Box 117)
    - Marketing and Media Decisions, 1980 (Box 117)
    - Mayor's Committee in the Public Interest, 1975 (Box 117)
    - New York Times articles written by Carl Spielvogel, 1953-1956 (Box 117)
    - Personal notes, correspondence, and documents, 1979-2000 (Box 117)
    - Post Information, Ljubluana, Slovenia, 2005-2009 (Box 117)
    - Photographs, 1980s-1990s (Box 117)
    - Pravda article, 2001 (Box 117)
    - Press, 1980-1984 (Box 117)
    - Ronald Reagan photograph, undated (Box 117)
    - Seven-Up materials, 1982 (Box 117)
    - Slovak Republic correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 117)
    - Spielvogel Star certificate, 1986 (Box 117)
    - Spielvogel star registration certificate, 1986; 4 items (Box 124)
      certificate with related documents
    - Travel photographs, undated (Box 117)
    - United Auto Group, 1997 (Box 117)
    - United States Department of State materials, 1994-1999 (Box 117)
    - Dried flowers and note, circa 1981 (Box 118)
    - Wedding scrapbook circa, 1981 (Box 118)
    - Who's Who in America?, 2005 (Box 119)
  - Vacations, 1965-2017; undated; 8
    Subseries contains travel itineraries, notes, printed matter, clippings, small artifacts such as boarding passes, photographs, correspondence, and financial papers from Diamonstein-Spielvogel's extensive international travels to locations such as Antarctica, China, India, England, South Africa and Spain, and others.
    Related materials are also located in the Travel Subseries of the Writings Series and in the Photographs Subseries of the Personal Files Series. Arranged alphabetically by location. Single photographs can be found throughout the folder contents, but larger groups are located at the end of the subseries and are arranged chronologically.
    - Antarctica and Argentina, 1986-1987 (Box 119)
    - Asia travel materials, 2005 (Box 119)
    - Barbaralee and Carl abroad, 2005 (Box 119)
    - Brussels trip, 1989-1990 (Box 119)
    - China, 1983 (Box 119)
    - China, 2004 (Box 119)
    - Cuba preservation materials, 1998-2002 (Box 119)
    - East Berlin and Prague, 1990 (Box 119)
    - Europe, 1965-1966 (Box 119)
    - Florida, 2005 (Box 120)
    - Hotel Ritz, Madrid, 1989 (Box 120)
    - India travel, 2010 (Box 120)
    - Italy correspondence, 1992 (Box 120)
    - Italy itinerary, 1985 (Box 120)
    - London, 1982-1986; 1993-1996; 3 folders (Box 120)
    - London shopping trip, 1982-1985; 2 folders (Box 120)
    - Nairobi, Kenya, Zimmerman Ltd., Taxidermy, undated (Box 120)
    - New Guinea primitive arts tour, 1992 (Box 120)
    - Sante Fe (Box 73)
    - Spain, 1989 (Box 120)
    - South Africa, Sandton Sun, 1991-1992 (Box 121)
    - South Africa trip, 1972 (Box 121)
    - South Africa trip, 1991 (Box 121)
    - South Africa trip, circa 1991 (Box 121)
    - Tahiti, undated (Box 121)
    - Theories of the Leisure Class, from Avenue Magazine (Box 72)
    - Travel postcards, undated (Box 121)
    - Travel plans and tickets, 2015 (Box 71)
    - Travel plans and tickets (Box 72)
    - Venice, 2015 (Box 71)
    - Vietnam and Japan, 1992 (Box 121)
    - Travel photographs: Africa, 1967 (Box 122)
    - Travel photographs: Norway/Sweden/Iceland, 1982 (Box 122)
    - Travel photographs, undated (Box 122)
    - Travel photographs, 1980s (Box 122)
    - Travel photographs, 1989-1992; 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Travel photographs, 1985; 1992-1996 (Box 608)
  - Wedding Artifacts and Scrapbooks, 1956; 1981-1982; 9
    Contains a metal engraving plate from Diamonstein-Spielvogel's first wedding to Alan Diamonstein in 1956 and two scrapbooks of memorabilia from her second wedding to Carl Spielvogel in 1981.
    - Caricature drawing from Wedding scrapbook 2, 1981-1982 (Box 124)
    - Diamonstein engagement engraving plate, 1956 (Box 123)
    - Wedding scrapbook 1, leaves 1-40, 1981; 19 folders (Box 123)
    - Wedding scrapbook 2, 1981-1982 (Box 123)
    - Clipping, wedding announcement, 1981 (Box 71)
  - Assorted Ephemera and Collectibles, 1950s-2000s; 10
    - Assorted souvenir tee shirts (t-shirts) from various political campaigns, events, and other activities. (Box 614)
    - Assorted souvenir tee shirts (t-shirts) and rubber wristband from events and other activities (Box 71)
    - Newspaper insert: "Celebrating Israel's Fifth Anniversary," New York Times, 16 pages, 1953 April 19 (Box 596)
      Large newspaper insert commemorating the fifth anniversary of the State of Israel; includes advertisements for businesses and hotels, a large section pertaining to fundraising through bonds; and a front-page statement by David ben-Gurion, Israeli Prime Minister.
    - Blank notecards, undated (Box 71)
    - Assorted business cards, undated (Box 74)
    - Passport (Box 71)
- Political Files, 1955-2017
  The relationship between art, culture, and public policy is highlighted by the materials in this series, which derive from Diamonstein-Spielvogel's political appointments under four U.S. presidents: Lyndon B. Johnson, Ronald Reagan, Bill Clinton, and Barack Obama. Formats present in the series include extensive notes, correspondence, meeting minutes, memoranda, printed matter, clippings, ledgers, photographs, official Certificates of Appointment, and small artifacts such as political pins. The materials also document Diamonstein-Spielvogel's political activities and interests on national and local levels.
  Diamonstein-Spielvogel served as a White House aide from 1963 to 1966 under President Lyndon B. Johnson's administration, and her political binders, notes and correspondence not only highlight the general political climate at the time, but also reveal her efforts to incorporate art and culture programs and initiatives into the Presidency. In her subsequent political appointments to the administrations of Presidents Reagan, Clinton and Obama, Diamonstein-Spielvogel was called upon for her expertise in the arts and public policy, as her correspondence and meeting materials attest.
  Divided into five subseries based on her appointments.
  - Johnson Appointment - White House Aide, 1955-2011; bulk 1959-1969; 1
    Subseries consists of correspondence, notes, clippings, official documents, small artifacts such as political pins, ledgers, memoranda, drafts, photographs, clippings, and printed matter pertaining to Diamonstein-Spielvogel's work as a White House Aide (1963-1966) to Eric Goldman under the Johnson administration. There is a small amount of materials documenting Diamonstein-Spielvogel's work for the TV series Open Mind, then hosted by Goldman, as well as drafts and correspondence from the writing of Goldman's book The Tragedy of Lyndon Johnson.
    Highlights also include materials surrounding the inauguration of the White House Fellows Program and the Presidential Scholars Program. Also of particular note is documentation of the first and only White House Festival of the Arts organized by Diamonstein-Spielvogel, which speaks to the interaction of art and politics. Other materials relevant to this series exist in small amounts in the Correspondence Series.
    The subseries is arranged chronologically. Two larger groupings of folders are present within this chronology: the Festival of the Arts group contains materials related to the White House Festival of the Arts and is arranged alphabetically; the White House Binders group contains folders of professional White House papers originally maintained in binders by Diamonstein-Spielvogel. Original order and folder titles have been retained.
    - General materials, 1955 and undated (Box 128)
    - Labor Day Speech/Youth Symposium 1959-1960, 1964 (Box 128)
    - White House photographs and pamphlet, circa 1960 (Box 128)
    - Eric Goldman memos, research, correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 128)
    - Library book checklist, 1960-1965 (Box 128)
    - Task force on education, 1961-1964 (Box 128)
    - White House Fellows, 1962-1965 (Box 129)
    - Status of women: Presidential Commission reports and other materials, 1963-1964 (Box 129)
      Contains a copy of American Women: Report of the President's Commission on the Status of Women, 1963; a copy of Progress Report on the Status of Women, October 11, 1963 through October 10, 1964; and a September 1964 memorandum to Eric Goldman from John Gardner on creating a new national commission on women as a follow-up; a few pieces of related correspondence; and copies of articles on the status of women in the U.S.
    - Graphic arts, 1963-1965 (Box 129)
    - Inaugurations research, circa 1963-1966 (Box 129)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson inauguration program (Box 77)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Correspondence, memorabilia, 1965-1967, 2 folders (Box 129)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Election eve/White House, 1965, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Goldman correspondence, memos, 1965-1966, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Goldman correspondence, memos, clippings, writings, 1965, 2 folders (Box 130)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Goldman resigns; Draft of portion of Johnson Book, 1966 (Box 130)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Lyndon Johnson, 1964-1966 (Box 131)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Lyndon Johnson II, 1964-1966, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Lyndon Johnson II, 1964-1966 - "LBJ Country," magazine article, circa 1964 (photocopy) (Box 132)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: LBJ Books, Bicentennial; Williamsburg Inter-Assembly, 1966, 2 folders (Box 131)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Mrs. Johnson, 1965 (Box 131)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Mrs. Johnson, Alabama, 1964-1966 (Box 131)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Inauguration, 1965-1966 (Box 133)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Inauguration, 1965: cover of Life magazine, photograph, clipping, 1965, 3 items (Box 132)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Lincoln Bedroom, the flag - Smithsonian, Bankers speech, Washington Monument, 1965-1966 (Box 133)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: McCall Corporation, "Womanpower" forum, 1968 (Box 133)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Memoranda, 1965, 2 folders (Box 133)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Metropolitan areas, beautification conservation, 1966, 2 folders (Box 133)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: National Committee on Draft; LBJ Princeton; 42-66 Elections; Mrs. J. - New England, 1966 (Box 133)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Photographs, Smithsonian and White House events, circa 1967 and undated (Box 134)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: President's Choice, 1965 (Box 134)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Presidential Scholars, 1966 (Box 134)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Presidential Scholars II, 1965-1967 (Box 134)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Eleanor Roosevelt portrait, 1966 (Box 134)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Transition to Cultural Affairs Commission, 1964-1968 (Box 134)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Travel photographs, 1960s (Box 134)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Vice president nominations, 1965-1966, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Thornton Wilder Book Medal; Medal of Freedom, 1963 (Box 135)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: White House Fellows, first, 1964, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: White House Festival of the Arts photographs, 1965 (Box 135)
    - White House Binders, 1963-1968: Writings by Eric Goldman and others, 1965-1966 (Box 135)
    - Agency letters of trade and professional organizations, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Artist biographies, circa 1964-1966 (Box 136)
    - College Student Leaders Meeting, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Copyright law, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence/notes, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Ellis Island, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Eric Goldman memos, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Goldwater Primer, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Photographs, memorabilia, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Professional societies, 1964 (Box 136)
    - Trade associations, 1964, 2 folders (Box 136)
    - Vice Presidency, 1964 (Box 137)
    - Eric Goldman memos, 1964 Sept.-1965 June (Box 137)
    - White House brochures, Presidential Scholars, White House Fellows and others, 1964-1965 (Box 137)
    - Family photographs at the White House, circa 1964-1966 (Box 137)
    - Eric Goldman memoranda, 1964-1966 (Box 137)
    - Open Mind, 1964-1966, folders 1-2 of 7 (Box 137)
    - Open Mind, 1964-1966, folders 3-7 of 7 (Box 138)
    - Larry Aldrich Museum, 1965 (Box 138)
    - Art in the Embassies program, United States Department of State, 1965 (Box 138)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 138)
    - Daily telephone calls, 1965 (Box 138)
    - Eric Goldman program suggestions, 1965 (Box 138)
    - Inauguration pins, 1965 (Box 139)
    - Memos, research for Goldman and correspondence, 1965 (Box 139)
    - 1964 Republican platform, circa 1965 (Box 139)
    - Political notes, circa 1965, 3 folders (Box 139)
    - Presidential inauguration clippings, photographs, 1965 (Box 139)
    - Presidential Scholars clippings, 1965 (Box 139)
    - United Nations, 1965 (Box 139)
    - White House Employment policies and pay, 1965-1966 (Box 140)
    - White House Festival of the Arts materials, 1965 (Box 140)
      Folders contain administrative and planning material related to 1965 Festival of the Arts programs on drama, film, ballet, photography, and poetry; materials include schedules, correspondence, financial matters, articles and reviews, clippings, guest lists, a scrapbook (two folders), the President's remarks at the Festival, and information on Saul Bellow, special guest. Includes a letter written home by Diamonstein-Spielvogel, describing the excitement of this important event on the arts.
    - White House Festival of the Arts materials, 1965 (Box 141)
    - White House Festival of the Arts scrapbook, 1965 (Box 142)